Finding Aid for Institute of Science and Technology (University of Michigan) records, 1950-1989.
Bentley Historical Library, University of Michigan
- Director's Office Files
  - circa 1979-1988
    (George Gamota)
    Office Files, ca. 1979-1988 (George Gamota) (8.5 linear feet) are arranged alphabetically. This series primarily documents the management of IST during the directorship of George Gamota, 1981-1986. Earlier files having continuing value to the director and his staff were also maintained here. Thus the researcher interested in the early history of IST should not overlook relevant documentation that this series might contain. The series has important sub-series that relate to the work of IST to develop and maintain contacts with outside governmental and industrial funding agencies, such as the Michigan Research Corporation and the Michigan Technology Council. Other sub-series concern the relationship of IST with the rest of the University of Michigan, respecting in part the development of programs in the areas of water research and ultra-small electronic studies.
    - Brochures
      - General (Box 7)
      - Brochure, 1978 (Box 7)
      - Brochure, 1982 (Box 7)
      - Brochure, 1983 (Box 7)
    - Director Search and Appointments
      - Director search, 1979 (Box 7)
      - Staff appointments (Box 7)
    - Directors' files (Box 8)
      - Joseph A. Boyd, 1960-1962 (Box 8)
      - James T. Wilson, 1962-1978 (Box 8)
      - Joseph J. Martin, 1978-1981 (Box 8)
      - George Gamota, 1981-1986 (Box 8)
      - W.C. Kelly, 1986-1987 (Box 8)
    - Activities/requests/suggestions
      - Requests to and from Gamota
        - Committee for Economic Development: Organizing for State Economic Progress, 1985 (Box 8)
        - Research opportunities, 1981-1985 (Box 8)
        - Requests to UM, 1985 (Box 8)
        - Entrepreneurial Initiatives in Developing Multidisciplinary Research Programs, 1981 (Box 8)
        - Graduate Fellowship Support, 1983 (Box 8)
      - Suggestions
        - Conference on Research and Manufacturing Industry in Michigan (proposed), 1981 (Box 8)
        - Proposal to create Senior Science & Engineering Advisory Board (SSEAB), 1984 (Box 8)
        - Computer Integrated Design and Manufacturing Systems (proposed), 1982 (Box 8)
        - Merger of the Office of the Vice President for Research and the Dean of the Graduate School, 1983-1984 (Box 8)
        - Proposed IST support of Medical School appointments, 1980-1981 (Box 8)
        - Miscellaneous (Box 8)
    - Office of the Vice President for Research (Linda Wilson)
      - IST background materials presented to LW upon her arrival, 1984-1985 (Box 8)
      - Background materials discussed with LW at meeting, July 1985 (Box 8)
      - Materials presented to LW re. IST units, December 1985 (Box 8)
    - Chronological file, July 1981 (Box 8)
    - IST retreat notebook, March 1982 (Box 8)
    - 25th anniversary celebration, 7 folders (Box 8)
    - Public Relations
      - Community Events (Box 8)
      - Congratulatory letters (Box 8)
      - Intel gift, 1982 (Box 8)
      - Media Services Survey (Box 8)
      - Memo to Michigan Citizens (newsletter) (Box 8)
      - Science Magazine, 1986 (Box 8)
      - Scientific American, 1982 (Box 8)
      - Slide Presentations (Box 8)
      - Surveys and inquiries, 2 folders (Box 8)
      - Television clip (used at half-time of UM football games, 1981) (Box 8)
      - UM press releases (Box 8)
      - University Record advertisements (Box 8)
    - University of Michigan Committees (Box 9)
      (Note: this subseries contains files predating Gamota's directorship)
      - Adaptive Systems Committee, 1960-1962 (Box 9)
      - Alumni Research Committee, 1983-1985 (Box 9)
      - Arms Control seminars, 1981-1982 (Box 9)
      - Automotive seminars, 1982 (Box 9)
      - Classified Research Committee, 1968-1985 (Box 9)
      - Collegiate Institute for Values and Science, 1983-1985 (Box 9)
      - Conflict of Interest, 1973-1984 (Box 9)
      - Department Administration Committee on Overhead, 1983-1984 (Box 9)
      - Distributed Data Entry Task Team, 1983-1984 (Box 9)
      - Energy Conservation Committee, 1984-1985 (Box 9)
      - Environmental Planning Council, 1976; 1981 (Box 9)
      - Environmental Research Institute of Michigan graduate program study, 1974 (Box 9)
      - Environmental Resources, Planning and Design, 1975-1976 (Box 9)
      - Government-University-Research Roundtable, 1985-1988 (Box 9)
      - Institute for Environmental Quality (Box 9)
      - Long Range Planning and Policy Recommendations (LS&A), 1964-1965 (Box 9)
      - Materials, Processing and Science, 1963 (Box 9)
      - Michigan's Inter-University Committee on Information Systems (MICIS), 1976-1984 (Box 9)
      - Microcomputer Policy, 1983 (Box 9)
      - National Oceanic Atmospheric Administration (NOAA) Building Committee, 1981 (Box 9)
      - North Campus Library Planning Committee, 1973 (Box 9)
      - Oceanography Review Committee, 1977 (Box 9)
      - Oceanography, Task Force for More Cohesive Program in, 1976-1978 (Box 9)
      - Program for Executive Exchange and Research, 1984 (Box 9)
      - Remote Sensing (graduate degree), 1965-1972 (Box 9)
      - Remote Sensing, UM/MSU Committee on, 1969-1972 (Box 9)
      - Remote Sensing Committee, 1985 (Box 9)
      - Research Advisory Council, 1983-1985; 3 folders (Box 9)
      - Research Club, 1982-1984 (Box 9)
      - Senate Advisory Committee on University Affairs (SACUA) (Box 10)
        - Classified research report, 1969-1971 (Box 10)
        - Job Security for Research Scientists, Ad hoc Committee on, 1980-1984 (Box 10)
      - Senate Advisory Committee on University Affairs (SACUA) (cont.)
        - Willow Run Laboratories, Research Policy Committee Report to Subcommittee on WRL, 1965 (Box 10)
      - School of Natural Resources Long Range Planning Committee, 1969-1970 (Box 10)
      - Space Physics, Review of, 1977-1978 (Box 10)
      - Space Research ad hoc committee, 1961-1962 (Box 10)
      - Transportation Research, Advisory Committee on, 1977 (Box 10)
      - Water Resources Program Committee, 1973-1981 (Box 10)
      - Water Sciences Review Committee, 1982 (Box 10)
      - Water Sciences: Committee to Discuss Interaction of Academic/Research Programs in Aquatic Areas, 1977-1981 (Box 10)
    - University of Michigan Issues
      - Classified and non-classified research policy, 1982-1986; 4 folders (Box 10)
      - Facilitating research, 1984 (Box 10)
      - Large Scale Interdisciplinary Research, 1983 (Box 10)
      - Nuclear Free Zone Act, 1984-1985 (Box 10)
      - Research ethics, 1982-1983 (Box 10)
      - Scholarship, integrity of, 1984-1987 (Box 10)
    - University of Michigan Programs
      - Applied Physics Program, 1985-1986 (Box 10)
      - Army Research Office proposals, 1982-1983 (Box 10)
      - Computer architecture/Massively Fault Tolerant Computational Structure, 1984 (Box 10)
      - Dioxin Study, 1983 (Box 10)
      - Economic Development activities and programs, 1983-1984; 2 folders (Box 10)
      - Energy Crisis, 1974-1975 (Box 10)
      - Energy Technology Development Program (ETDP) (Michigan Dept. of Commerce), 1980-1981 (Box 10)
      - Equipment Corporations, 1983 (Box 10)
      - Equipment proposals, 1983-1984
        - General, 1981-1984; 3 folders (Box 10)
        - Electron Spectrometer for Chemical Analysis, 1982 (Box 10)
        - Electron Microbeam Analysis Laboratory, 1983-1984 (Box 10)
      - Exploratory Energy Research Program, 1981; 1984 (Box 10)
      - Fellowship Programs, 1987 (Box 11)
      - Ground vehicles, 1982 (Box 11)
      - Hazardous waste, 1984 (Box 11)
      - High Energy Physics, 1983 (Box 11)
      - Industrial Affiliates Program, 1984 (Box 11)
      - Information Transfer on Japanese Industry, 1982 (Box 11)
      - Large Scale Interdisciplinary Research Programs, 1983 (Box 11)
      - Manufacturing: Proposal "Sociotechnical Innovations for Computer-Aided Manufacturing", 1981 (Box 11)
      - Managerial Production Task Force, 1981-1983 (Box 11)
      - Managerial Productivity Proposal, 1982 (Box 11)
      - Manufacturing Technology (Conference on Managing Manufacturing Technology through the 1990s), 1983 (Box 11)
      - Materials Science, 1983 (Box 11)
      - Microelectronics, 1980-1981 (Box 11)
      - Microelectronics Systems (ECE), 1981 (Box 11)
      - Molecular Genetics, 1981-1982; 4 folders (Box 11)
      - Particle Beam and Pulsed Power Research, 1981 (Box 11)
      - Quality Assurance Efforts with the Automobile Industry, 1983 (Box 11)
      - Rackham Fellowships (Box 11)
      - Reliability, 1982-1983 (Box 11)
      - Remote Sensing, 1985-1987; 3 folders (Box 11)
      - Research and Development Limited Partnerships, 1983 (Box 11)
      - Research Internships (internships in research) (Box 11)
      - Robotics, 1981-1982 (Box 11)
      - Software Development Research, 1981-1983; 2 folders (Box 11)
      - Software Engineering Institute Proposal, 1983-1985; 4 folders (Box 11)
      - Software Engineering Institute Proposal, 1983-1985; 4 folders (Box 12)
      - Space Station, 1982-1983 (Box 12)
      - Space Station Workshop, 1983 (Box 12)
      - Space Studies
        - Project COBRA, 1982 (Box 12)
        - Project GENESIS, 1980 (Box 12)
      - Super Computers (proposed Center for Scientific Computation), 1983; 1985 (Box 12)
      - Superconducting Super Collider, 1983-1984 (Box 12)
      - Surface Studies, 1982-1983; 4 folders (Box 12)
      - Title XII Conference, 1977-1988 (Box 12)
      - University Consortium on Transportation, 1982 (Box 12)
      - University-Industry Linkages in Michigan, 1982-1983 (Box 12)
      - UM/Industry Relations
        - "Encouraging New Technological Development in the Greater Ann Arbor Community" (background materials), 1980-1982 (Box 12)
        - Technology-based Committee to the Academic Council, 1980 (Box 12)
        - "Planning an Increased Interaction between the University of Michigan and Industry and Business,", 1979 (Box 12)
        - Discussion paper for Governor William Milliken re. Michigan's high-technology industries, 1980 (Box 12)
      - Urban and Regional Planning (Box 12)
      - Urban Mass Transportation Administration, 1982-1986; 6 folders (Box 13)
      - US/Japanese Auto Study, 1982 (Box 13)
      - Ultra-Small Electronics Research Project (USER)
        - History, 1981-1983 (Box 13)
        - Capabilities of the staff, 1981 (Box 13)
        - Proposal: "A multidisciplinary approach to the science and technology of sub-micron electronics,", 1982 (Box 13)
        - Proposal: "A multidisciplinary approach...., 1983 (Box 13)
        - Comments regarding sub-micron proposal, 1982 (Box 13)
        - Presentations, 1982 (Box 13)
        - Proposal: "Studies of chemical mechanism, mass, and charge transport in chemically sensitive electronic devices," 2 versions, 1982 (Box 13)
        - Comments regarding chemical mechanism proposal, 1982-1983 (Box 13)
      - Water Resources
        - Director search, 1966-1967 (Box 13)
        - Environmental Protection Agency negotiations, 1972-1973 (Box 13)
        - Federal Water Pollution Control Agency negotiations, 1967-1969 (Box 13)
        - Graduate Program, 1965-1966 (Box 13)
        - Program interests, 1967-1973 (Box 13)
        - Water Resources Center-plans, 1967-1969 (Box 13)
        - Water Resources Committee minutes, 1966-1977 (scattered) (Box 13)
        - Water Resource/Sea Grant Programs/Great Lakes Division, 1970-1976 (Box 13)
    - Contacts: Companies/Organizations (Box 14)
      - Coalition for Advancing Industrial Technology (Box 14)
      - Detroit Edison, 1984-1985 (Box 14)
      - General Dynamics, 1981-1984 (Box 14)
      - General Electric: CAD/CAM applications, 1981-1982 (Box 14)
      - Government-University-Industry Research Roundtable (Box 14)
      - Great Lakes Governors' Conference, 1983 (Box 14)
      - Industrial Technology Institute (ITI), 1982 (Box 14)
      - International Business Machines, 1982 (Box 14)
      - Japanese Biotechnology guests visits (Box 14)
      - Kellogg Company, 1983 (Box 14)
      - MAZDA, 1985 (Box 14)
      - Michigan Biotechnology Institute
        - General (Box 14)
        - Molecular Biology report of the Governor's Task Force, 1982 (Box 14)
      - Michigan High Technology Task Force, 1985 (Box 14)
      - Michigan Research Corporation
        - General, 1983-1987 (Box 14)
        - Advisory Committee, 1984 (Box 14)
        - Board of Directors meetings, 1983-1984 (Box 14)
        - Hancock/Crockett report, 1982-1983; 2 folders (Box 14)
        - Howe report, 1981 (Box 14)
        - Intra Gene International, 1982 (Box 14)
        - Mid-America Seed Capital Fund, 1985 (Box 14)
        - Neogen Corporation, 1981-1982 (Box 14)
        - Newspaper clippings/news releases (Box 14)
        - Profit/non-profit issue, 1983 (Box 14)
        - Project, 1984 (Box 14)
      - Michigan Technology Council
        - General (Box 14)
        - Agendas (Box 14)
        - Board of directors; members (lists) (Box 14)
        - Bylaws, organizational structure, and overview (Box 14)
        - Cash basis financial statement (Box 14)
        - Michigan Technology Fair, 1983-1985 (Box 14)
        - Minutes (Box 14)
        - Policy, job specification, and membership fee (Box 14)
        - Programs and seminars (Box 14)
        - Proposals (Box 14)
        - Publications (Box 14)
        - Survey of High Technology Firms in the Ann Arbor Area, 1983 (Box 14)
        - Venture Center (Box 14)
      - Minority Technology Council of Michigan (MYCM) (Box 14)
      - National Science Foundation (Box 14)
      - University Corporation for Atmospheric Research, 1976-1985 (Box 14)
    - Contacts: Governments
      - Local
        - Mayor's Energy Advisory Board, 1982 (Box 15)
      - State
        - Review of draft reports: "Michigan Locational Analysis for Technology Based Firms and Technology" and "A Program to Encourage the Growth of Technology Based Firms in Michigan" (1982) (Box 15)
        - Michigan Economic Development Authority, 1982-1983 (Box 15)
        - Defense procurement for Michigan, 1983-1984 (Box 15)
        - Michigan Department of Commerce, 1982-1985 (Box 15)
        - Michigan Mindpower II Conference, 1984-1985 (Box 15)
        - New and Emerging Technologies (NET), 1986 (Box 15)
        - Superior Township Research Park (possible state-funded building), 1983 (Box 15)
      - Federal
        - Office of the Deputy Under Secretary of Defense for Research and Engineering, 1983 (Box 15)
        - National Research Council: Survey of Physics in the, 1980s; 1983 (Box 15)
        - Office of Naval Research, 1984 (Box 15)
        - Technology International Council, 1983-1986 (Box 15)
    - Contacts: People
      - Pickens, T. Boone, 1987 (Box 15)
      - Pollack, Lana, 1985 (Box 15)
      - Power, Philip, 1982-1984 (Box 15)
      - Sederburg, William, 1985 (Box 15)
      - Walsh, Tom (Air Force Office of Scientific Research), 1982 (Box 15)
    - Speeches/Presentations, 1981-1984; 52 folders (Box 15)
    - Speeches/Presentations, 1985-1986; 20 folders (Box 16)
- Unit Files
  Unit Files, 1959-1987 (0.6 linear feet) consists of files for the various IST research units. These records appear to be the administrative files kept by the individual units. This series should be used in conjunction with the two series of OFFICE FILES. The importance of this series is its documentation of the management of the separate units, mainly water and highway transportation research.
  - Great Lakes and Marine Waters Center
    - Director (Box 16)
    - General (Box 16)
    - Proposed merger with Department of Atmospheric and Oceanic Science, 1983-1984 (Box 16)
  - Great Lakes and Marine Waters Center (cont.)
    - Coordination of aquatic science activities at the UM, 1974-1983 (Box 16)
    - Space needs (Box 16)
    - International program: proposed activity with AID, 1983 (Box 16)
    - Account and budget information, 1981-1982 (Box 16)
    - Transmission Electron Microscope (TEM), 1986-1988 (Box 16)
    - Mass Spectrometer, 1981-1985 (Box 16)
    - Committees
      - Advisory Committee, 1975-1976 (Box 16)
      - Executive Committee, 1976-1987 (Box 16)
      - Management Committee, 1976 (Box 16)
      - Great Lakes Research Administrators, 1977 (Box 16)
      - Michigan Sea Grant Policy Committee, 1976-1986 (Box 16)
      - Michigan Sea Grant Management Team, 1986 (Box 16)
  - Great Lakes Resource Management Program
    - General, 1975-1979 (Box 16)
    - Coastal Zone Laboratory (CZL)
      - General, 1972-1976 (Box 16)
      - Research papers (Box 16)
    - Grants and contracts
      - Outstanding proposals, 1976-1978 (Box 16)
      - Wrap-up of various contracts (Box 17)
      - Wastewater project, 1974-1975 (Box 17)
      - Great Lakes Environmental Data and Information Center, 1975-1977 (Box 17)
      - U.S. Army Corps of Engineers, 1975-1978 (Box 17)
    - Grants and contracts (cont.)3
      - Armstrong: Assignment agreement for Marine Information Systems Services, 1977-1978 (Box 17)
      - Goodyear Tire and Rubber, 1976-1977 (Box 17)
      - Demonstration Erosion Control Project, 1977 (Box 17)
      - Ship support/ship operations, 1973-1975 (Box 17)
      - Facilities for Great Lakes Research (withdrawn), 1972-1973 (Box 17)
      - Upper Great Lakes Program (withdrawn), 1971-1972 (Box 17)
      - National Oceanographic Laboratory System, 1970-1972 (Box 17)
  - Great Lakes Research Division
    - General (Box 17)
    - Account and budget information (Box 17)
    - Advisory Council (Box 17)
    - $55 Million Program, 1965-1966 (Box 17)
    - Vessels
      - General, 1961-1988 (Box 17)
      - National Science Foundation
        - Grants for operating expenses, 1966-1972 (Box 17)
        - Marine technician support, 1974-1975 (Box 17)
      - R/V (research vessel) Inland Seas
        - General, 1961-1975 (Box 17)
        - Efforts to replace, 1972-1974 (Box 17)
      - R/V Highland Lassie, 1963-1967 (Box 18)
      - R/V Naiad, 1963-1966 (Box 18)
      - Coast Guard Cutter Tamarack, 1970 (Box 18)
      - R/V Maple, 1973-1975 (Box 18)
      - R/V Mysis (Box 18)
      - R/V Laurentian, 6 folders (Box 18)
      - Docking arrangements, 1962-1987 (Box 18)
      - 1976 U-M Ship Scheduling Committee, 1976 (Box 18)
      - Ship time (Box 18)
      - Regional Scheduling Committee, 1973-1974 (Box 18)
      - Operation Submich, 1964-1968 (Box 18)
  - University of Michigan Transportation Research Institute (UMTRI)
    - General, 1966-1987 (Box 18)
    - Director search, 1984-1987 (Box 18)
    - Interim management, 1985-1987 (Box 18)
    - Assistant director search, 1985 (Box 18)
    - Committees
      - Advisory Council, 1970-1976 (Box 18)
      - Executive Committee, 1966-1987 (Box 18)
      - Faculty Advisory, 1966 (Box 19)
      - Faculty Program Advisory, 1966 (Box 19)
    - Building, 1969-1974 (Box 19)
    - Grants and contracts, 1978-1987 (Box 19)
    - Miscellaneous administrative problems, 1985-1987 (Box 19)
    - History
      - Clippings and news releases, 1966-1975 (Box 19)
      - College of Engineering relationship, 1966; 1987 (Box 19)
      - Original proposal (and directorship), 1965-1971 (Box 19)
      - Name change, 1982 (Box 19)
    - Programs
      - General, 1970-1987 (Box 19)
      - Proposed, 1970-1977 (Box 19)
      - Biomedical, 1966; 1985 (Box 19)
      - Center for Injury Control Studies (proposed), 1984-1986 (Box 19)
      - Department of Transportation Maritime Administration Ship, 1984-1985 (Box 19)
      - Fellowships, 1967-1986 (Box 19)
      - Industrial Affiliation Program, 1987 (Box 19)
      - Michigan Transportation Research Program, 1974-1982 (Box 19)
      - NASA Center of Excellence in Man Systems Research, 1984-1986 (Box 19)
      - Off-Road Test Facility, 1968-1971 (Box 19)
      - Office for the Study of Automotive Transportation
        - General, 1978-1987 (Box 19)
        - Cooperative Automotive Research Program (CARP), 1978-1987 (Box 19)
        - Chevrolet-Pontiac-Canada Group, 1985 (Box 19)
      - Rehabilitation Engineering Center, 1982-1983 (Box 19)
      - Sub-contract with Mid-America Research Institute, 1980-1985 (Box 19)
      - Toyota negotiations, 1981-1984 (Box 19)
      - University Transportation Center, 1987 (Box 19)
      - Urban, Technological, and Environmental Planning (relationship with), 1983-1985 (Box 19)
    - UMTRI Retreat, 1986 (Box 19)
  - Michigan Sea Grant College Program
    - General (Box 20)
    - Ad hoc committee to review interest in Sea Grant, 1968 (Box 20)
    - Advisory Committee (to write first Sea Grant Proposal), 1968-1969 (Box 20)
    - Advisory Committee, 1975-1976 (Box 20)
    - Application for Sea Grant College status, 1982 (Box 20)
    - Audits, 1973-1983; 3 folders (Box 20)
    - Canale, Raymond, problem, 1975-1977 (Box 20)
    - Chronological file, 1986-1987 (Box 20)
    - Congressional act, 1967-1975 (Box 20)
    - Congressional hearings and other efforts, 1976-1984 (Box 20)
    - Correspondence with other schools, 1967-1975 (Box 20)
    - Correspondence (prior to 1975 site visit), 1970-1974, 1970-1975 (Box 20)
    - Cost sharing, 1970-1974 (Box 20)
    - Director search, 1968 (Box 20)
    - Environmental Protection Agency, letter of intent to, 1980 (Box 20)
    - Extension Program Leader, MSU, 1986 (Box 20)
    - Future plans, 1986 (Box 20)
    - General fund, 1979-1986 (Box 20)
    - Grand Traverse Bay, 1975-1976 (Box 20)
    - Great Lakes Basin Commission, interaction with, 1976-1977 (Box 20)
    - Impact of program on state of Michigan, 1981 (Box 20)
    - Indirect coast rate, 1975-1976 (Box 20)
    - Insurance, licenses, etc., 1974-1976 (Box 20)
    - Marine Division, National Association of State Universities and Land Grant Colleges, 1983 (Box 20)
    - Muskegon Project, 1976 (Box 20)
    - Planning for Sea Grant Office, history, etc., 1966-1972 (Box 20)
    - Policy Committee, 1982-1986 (Box 20)
    - Sea Grant Program Advisory Services, 1976 (Box 21)
    - Sea Grant proposal, 1985-1989 (Box 21)
    - Sea Grant Association, membership, 1974-1986 (Box 21)
    - Site visit, 1975 (Box 21)
    - University of Wisconsin cooperation, 1975 (Box 21)
  - Electro-Optics Science Laboratory
    - General, 1963-1967 (Box 21)
    - Budget, 1963-1966 (Box 21)
    - Building file, 1963-1966 (Box 21)
    - HEW proposal, 1964 (Box 21)
    - Reprints, clippings etc., 1964-1967 (Box 21)
    - Sponsored Research activity, 1964-1965 (Box 21)
  - Engineering Psychology Laboratory, 1962-1977 (Box 21)
  - MERIT Computer Network
    - General, 1969-1988 (Box 21)
    - Account and budget information, 1979-1985; 2 folders (Box 21)
    - Board of Directors minutes, 1980-1981 (Box 21)
    - Space needs, 1980 (Box 21)
    - UMNET, circa 1983 (Box 21)
  - Special Projects Division
    - General, 1985-1987 (Box 21)
    - Crockett/Krzyzowski activities, 1982-1987 (Box 21)
    - Office of International Peace and Security Research, 1982-1987 (Box 21)
    - Proposed review, 1985-1986 (Box 21)
    - Robotics Museum, proposed, 1985 (Box 21)
    - Space needs, 1983-1988 (Box 21)
    - Transition, 1988 (Box 21)
  - Ultrasmall Structure Research Office
    - General, 1982-1986 (Box 21)
    - Equipment (Box 21)
    - Proposal preparation, 1984 (Box 21)
    - Submicron structures workshop (Box 21)
    - Visitors, 1984-1985 (Box 21)
- Chronological File
  The Chronological File, 1960-1984 (0 3 linear feet) is comprised of photocopies of outgoing administrative correspondence of the directors and associate directors of IST.
  - 1960-1966 (Box 22)
  - 1967-1976 (Box 23)
  - 1977-1984 (Box 24)
  - Willow Run Chronological file, 1960-1963 (Box 24)
- Proposal File